Guide to the Fernando Alegria Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1. Correspondence
  - Subseries A. Authors
    - [Unidentified], Beatriz (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - [Unidentified], Daniel (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - [Unidentified], David (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - [Unidentified], Elizabeth (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - [Unidentified], George (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - [Unidentified], Gladys (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - [Unidentified], Heather (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - [Unidentified], Henry (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - [Unidentified], John (Box 7, Folder 45)
      Includes Nota preliminar: tms, n.d. / by Augusto Roa Bastos
    - [Unidentified], Jorge (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - [Unidentified], Juan (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - [Unidentified], Juli (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - [Unidentified], Lautaro (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - [Unidentified], Lennart (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - [Unidentified], Leticia (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - [Unidentified], Luis (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - [Unidentified], Magda (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - [Unidentified], Marcia (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - [Unidentified], Marius (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - [Unidentified], Mary (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - [Unidentified], Matilde (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - [Unidentified], [Mike?] (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - [Unidentified], Nestor (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - [Unidentified], Nicholasa (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - [Unidentified], Nina (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - [Unidentified], Paula (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - [Unidentified], Pauline (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - [Unidentified], Raul (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - [Unidentified], Richard (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - [Unidentified], Toby (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - [Unidentified] (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - [Unidentified] (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - [Unidentified] (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Subseries B. Publishers & Presses
    - Agencia Literaria Anne-Marie Vallat (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Americas Magazine. Receipt of payment 1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ANSA News Agency (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Arte Publico (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Barral Editores (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Biblioteca Ayacucho (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Carmen Balcells / Agencia Literaria (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Casa de las Americas (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Chandos Music (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Cine Accion (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Crossing Press (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Cuaderno Americanos. "El poeta que se volvió gusano" (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - D.C. Heath and Co. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Deborah Dickson Films (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Desde la Gente Ediciones (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Diraci (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Edicion Ayacucho del Canto General (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Ediciones de la Flor (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Ediciones del Norte (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Ediciones Destino, S.L. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Editora Brasilense, S.A. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Editores Alemanas [German editors] (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Editores Rumanos [Rumanian, Czheckoslovakian editors] (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Editorial Grijalbo (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Editorial Juridica de Chile (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Editorial Laia, S.A., Barcelona (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Editorial Nueva Imagen (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Editorial Universitaria (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Educators Publishing (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Empresa Editora Zig-Zag, S.A. (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Empresa Editora Zig-Zag, S.A.: liquidaciones (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Eudeba [Editorial Universitaria de Buenos Aires] (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Farrar & Rhinehart, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Fondations Simon I. Patiño (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Fondo de Cultura Economica, Chile (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Fondo de Cultura Economica, Mexico (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Fondo El Libro del Pueblo, Pan American Union (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - F.S. Crofts & Co. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Fundacion Biblioteca Ayacucho (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - La Garza Morena (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Holt, Rinehart, and Winston, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Institute Literario y Cultural Hispanico (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Janney, Frank. Ediciones del Norte (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - K. Thienemanns Verlag (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Las Americas - Anaya (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Latin American Literary Review Press (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Librarie STOCK "Atout Cheval" (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Libreria Teresa Martinez Edelmiro Gonzalez Sucesores, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - LITA (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - McGraw-Hill (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - The New Press (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Nueva Imagen (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Odyssey Review (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Peace and Gladness Co-op Press (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Posdata de Concepcion (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Princeton Encyclopedia of Poetry and Poetics (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Puerto Rico (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Retratos Contemporaneos - Autorizaciones (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Siglo XXI - Mexico (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Sociedad Chilena de Estudios Literarios (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Stanford University Press re: Allende: mi vecino el presidente (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Stanford University Press re: La rebelión de los placeres (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Studium Andrea (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Taller de Escritores [1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Taller de Escritores [2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Taller de Escritores: introduccion a la antologia y discurso del rector (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Universidad de Concepcion: correspondencia general [general correspondence] (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Universidad de Costa Rica (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - University of Saint Thomas (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Subseries C. General
    - [Abalost?], Carmen (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Academia Iberoamericana de Poesia (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Academia Norteamericana de la Lengua Española (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - [Agricon-Chavez?], Carlos (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Alegria, Fernando. ALS, 1934 Apr. 25 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Alegria, Fernando. TLS: New York, to Distinguido Señor, 1938 Aug. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Aponte, Rachel (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Asociacion Chilena de Escritores (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Bandera Productions (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Benavides, Rosamel re: Juan Epple (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Boarman, Vivian (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - [Bouolart?], Michel and Marina (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Bradley, Susan (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Bronstein, William (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Chase, William. Assoc. Dean, Humanities and Sciences, Stanford Univ. (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Chile California Foundation (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Chile. Consulado General = Consulate General (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Chile. Departamento de Programas Culturales (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Chile. Direccion de Bibliotecas, Archivos, y Museos. Seccion Referencias Criticas (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Chile. Division de Cultura (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Chile. Embajada = Embassy (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Chile Democratico (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Cochran, Kent (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Congreso Internacional de Literatura Feminina (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Dialogo Asociación Civil (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Diaz Lacayo, Aldo (Nicaraguan Embassador) (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Dvoredsky, Jose (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Ensignia C., Moises (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Flach, Martina (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Frances, Anthony A. (Box 10, Folder 32.5)
    - Fundacion Pablo Neruda (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Fundacion Victor Jara (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Gaceta Municipal (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Gowdy, Barbara (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Hardy de Shetjman, Clarisa (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Hepburn, Beverly (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Houskova, Anna (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Howard University (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - International Writers and Artists Association (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Jakob, Maura (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Johnson, John (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Karol, Jorge (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Kaufman, Rhoda (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Lanain, [Ly?] (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Lopez, Carlos (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - M. de Trigueros y "VISA" (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Madar, W. Chase (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Mayfield, Lois [girlfriend] 1941 - 1943 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - McLean, J.H. (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Moorehead, Robert (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Morales, Alejandro (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Navarro, Arturo (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Ornego, Teresa (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Oyarzun de Aylwin, Leonor (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Pan American Union (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Pesich, Robert S. (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Prado, E. (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Quintanilla, Luis (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Reilly, Sister Philip Mary (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Rojas Gomez, Patricia (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Sociedad Chilena de Estudios Literarios 1987 Mar. 17 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Sociedad de Escritores de Chile (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Solanum, Helen (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Stanford Amnesty International (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Stanford University (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Strassburg, Robert (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Turner, Ines (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Union de Escritores Jovenes (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Universidad Austral de Chile (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Western Institute for Social Research (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Invitations (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Invitations (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with academic institutions (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Adhesiones, cartas, etc. sobre Neruda, Chile, Allende = Attachments, letters, etc. re: Neruda, Chile, Allende [1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Adhesiones, cartas, etc. sobre Neruda, Chile, Allende = Attachments, letters, etc. re: Neruda, Chile, Allende [2 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - El paso de los gansos: cartas (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Revista Ibero Americana (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Cartas de estudiantes = Letters from students (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Cartas de recommendacion = Letters of recommendation (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Recommendations (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Recommendations (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Recommendations (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Recommendations (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Postcards: F-M (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Postcards: N-Z (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Subseries D. Family
    - Alegria, Carmen D. [daughter] (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Alegria, Daniel [son] (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Alegria, Dylan [grandson] (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Alegria, Julio [brother] (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Alegria, Manuel [grandson] (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Alegria, Santiago [brother] (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Alegria, Santiago [father] (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - [ ], George [nephew] (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - [ ], Sam [grandson] (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - [Unidentified grandson] (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Series 2. Manuscripts by Alegria
  - Alegria, Fernando. 4 de Nov. 1971: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. ¿A que lado de la cortina?: ams, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Abel Posse on his fiction: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Acuarios: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Adios, Medusa, por Luis Sanchez Torres: [review]: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Alfonso Calderon: Isla de los bienaventurados: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Alicia Galaz Vivar: tms, n.d., 8 p. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Allende, mi vecino el presidente: table of contents and chapter drafts, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Allende, mi vecino el presidente: research materials, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Allende, mi vecino el presidente: outline & related correspondence, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Allende, mi vecino el presidente: chapters VII & X with letter from from Asa Zatz (translator), 1988 Feb. 18 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Allende, mi vecino el presidente: ms, notes, & interview with Tencha Allende, ca. 1983 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Allende, mi vecino el presidente: mss, notes, research materials n.d. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Alsino: Mision Imposible: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Alturas de Macchu Picchu: utopia de un pasado heroico: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Aluvión de fuego [por] O. Cerruto: ams, ca. 1935 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Amor y desamor, la poesia de Enrique Lihn: tms, n.d., 17 p. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Angel Rama, Marta Traba: Los Adioses: tms (photocopy), n.d., 3 p. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Answers: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Anti-imperialismo de dos clases: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Antologia: copias y traducciones: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Antonio Benitez Rojo: Estatuas [sepulbados?]: holograph mss, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Includes letter by Antonio Benitez Rojo.
  - Alegria, Fernando. Aporte de la mujer al nuevo lenguaje poético de Latinoamerica. -- p. 27-35. -- In Revista/Review Interamericana. -- Vol. 12, no. 1 1982 Spring (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Apuntes de un lugareño: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Los arboles de Raimundo Way: José Revueltas: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El arte de Pablo Neruda: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El asesinato de Letelier en Washington: un testimonio revelador, n.d., 8 p. (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Atahualpa Yupanqui: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Autorretrato: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - La aventura y el nombre: antologia de tres novelistas chilenos / Rojas, Alegria, Lafourcade n.d. (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Azul ..., Dario en Chile: tms, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Begin the Beguine ¿para que?: tms, n.d., 3 p. (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Between doing what it takesand not doing it: tms with annotations, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Blind master of the guided dream n.d. (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Borges' Song of myself: tms & tls, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Caballo de copas: cover art, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Caballo de copas. -- p. 29. -- In Circulo de Lectores. 1975 July - Sept. (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Calles: ams, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Camaleon: tms [1 of 2] n.d., (cy 1) (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Camaleon: tms [2 of 2] n.d., (cy 1) (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Camaleon: tms [1 of 2] n.d., (cy 2) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Camaleon: tms [2 of 2] n.d., (cy 2) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Canal zone [por] D. Aguilera Malta: ams, ca. 1935 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Canción de la Unidad Popular: tms, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Canta madre: tms, n.d., 1 p. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cantata de Allende, Muerte, y resurreccion: tms, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [Carlos Fuentes]: tms, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Carlos Pezoa Veliz: tms, n.d., 13 p. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Carlos Pezoa Veliz: tms, ca. 1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Includes facsimile coversheet.
  - Alegria, Fernando. Carlos Pezoa Veliz: tms, ca. 1991, 14 p. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Carnaval: la dictadura y el exilio: tms, n.d., 36 p. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Carnaval: la dictadura y el exilio: tms, n.d., 21 p. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Carpentier: war of time: tms, n.d., 3 p. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Celia Correas de Zapata: Tiempo ajeno: tms, n.d., 4 p. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Changing times. -- (Pajandrum Broadside). -- [S.l.]: Pajandrum Press, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Chile: bibliography: tms, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Chile: ciencia y ficcion: tms, n.d., 5 p. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Chile: photographs / by Michael Bry; text by Fernando Alegria n.d. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [Chilean literature]: tms, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. ¡Ciao, Il bosco!: tms, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. ¡Ciao, Il bosco!: tms, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. ¡Ciao, Il bosco!: tms, n.d., 42 p. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Alegria, Fernando. ¡Ciao, Il bosco!: ams, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cine: treatment, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Circulo de Sheridan: ams, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El circulo de Sheridan: tms, n.d., 11 p. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Columbus' journal: tms / prologue by Gregorio Marañon n.d., 2 copies (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [Con un dedo ... ]: untitled ams, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Conjugando el verbo ser: tms, n.d., 1 p. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Contemporary Spanish American fiction: tms, n.d., 9 p. (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Coral de guerra: ams, 1979, 36 p. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Coral de guerra: 1a version: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Coral de guerra: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cortazar, el torito, y el tani: tms, n.d., 7 p. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cortazar, el torito, y el tani: tms, n.d., 7 p. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cortazar, el torito, y el tani: tms, n.d., 9 p. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cuando cantan los poetas: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cuando sali de mi patria. -- p. 2. -- In Uno Mas Uno n.d. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cuando sali de mi patria. -- In Sabado 1982 Mar. 27 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Un cuarto de siglo con Allende: tms, n.d., 21 p. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cuatro tanques: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cuba nos manda azucar: tms, n.d., 2 p. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cuecas: tms & ams, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cuentos: copias: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cuentos para una iglesia desesperada: ams, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Cultura y dictadura en Chile: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The curse of the enlightened tyrant: tms, n.d., 8 p. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The curse of the enlightened tyrant: tms, n.d., 12 p. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [Daniel Casanueva]: tms, n.d., 10 p. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Dario en Chile: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. De esto no me muero: tms, n.d., 21 p. (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The dead man's bride: tms, n.d., 3 p. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Definiciones de un exilio: tms, n.d., 9 p. (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Delia Dominguez (1931): tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El descubrimiento de America y el redescubrimiento de España: tms, n.d., 7 p. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El descubrimiento de America y el redescubrimiento de España: tms, n.d., 9 p. (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Dia tras dia: [review]: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Dialogo de rara intención: un cuaderno: ams, n.d., 15 p. (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Dialogo de sordos: tms, n.d., 1 p. (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Dialogue with C. Fuentes: tms, n.d., 5 p. (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Diario de vidas: tms, n.d., 4 p. (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The discovery of America and the rediscovery of Spain: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Alegria, Fernando. The discovery of America and the rediscovery of Spain: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Discurso en llave de O para el docto Nelson Osorio: tms, n.d., 1 p. (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Don Eugenio: tms, n.d., 4 p. (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Alegria, Fernando. E. Mallea, reviews of works by n.d. (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Ecue-Yamba-O! [por] Alejo Carpentier: ams & tms, ca. 1933 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Elegia a Manuel Antonio Borja: clipping (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Elite y contracultura: proyecciones políticas de la vanguardia hispanoamericana. -- p. 61-66 n.d. (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Alegria, Fernando. En 1969 volé en un Boeing DC-8 ... :fragment tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [En estos dias .... ]: untitled tms, n.d., 16 p. (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Los engaños de Tremont: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Enrique Huaco: tms, n.d., 6 p. (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Enrique Lihn: tms, n.d., 12 p. (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Entrevista: tms, n.d., 8 p. (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Entrevista con Eric: tms, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Entrevista con J.A. Epple: tms & tls, 1982 - 1985 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El escritor chileno y la revolucion: clipping (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Alegria, Fernando. [Ese y Esa: comedia en un acto]: tms, n.d., 25 p. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Ese y Esa: comedia en un acto: tms, n.d., 28 p. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Ese y Esa: comedia en un acto: tms, n.d., 34 p. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Ese y Esa: comedia en un acto: tms, 1990, 35 p. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Ese y Esa: comedia en un acto: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Ese y Esa: comedia en un acto: tms: p. 98-128, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Una especie de memoria: ams & tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Una especie de memoria. -- p. 11-15. -- In Una especie de memoria. -- Mexico: Editorial Nueva Imagen, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Esperanza y desesperanza de Chile: tms, n.d., 6 p. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Esquinazo del Guerrillero: tms, n.d., 1 p. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El estado y el poeta, un arte de resistencia: tms (photocopy) with holograph annotations, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El estado y el poeta, un arte de resistencia: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El estado y el poeta, un arte de resistencia: tms, n.d., 14 p. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Alegria, Fernando. El estado y el poeta, un arte de resistencia: tms, n.d., 14 p. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Estilo de novelar o estilos de vivir: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Eugenio Brito (1950): tms, n.d., 6 p. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Eva Luna by Isabel Allende: [review]: tms, n.d., 6 p. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Eva Luna: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Los factores culturales en la cooperación de America Latina: identidad y rivalidad: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Alegria, Fernando. La familia Parra: tms, n.d., 34 p. (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Farabundo went to war: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Gabriela: tms, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Gabriela Mistral (1889-1957): tms, n.d., 32 p. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Garcia Lorca pasa por Rancagua: tms, n.d., 21 p. (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Garcia Lorca pasa por Rancagua: tms, n.d., 30 p. (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Alegria, Fernando. Garcia Marquez: Macondo: tms, n.d., 16 p. (Box 15, Folder 27)